Bertin "Ben" Koala

ben.koala123@gmail.com

Tel:

SUMMARY

Focused and quick-learning Full stack Engineer with one year of experience in web design using javascript programming, html, css and various frameworks and databases. Managed various projects to implement multiple websites working with consulting companies. I have also led multiple projects for the acquisition of tools and equipment used in RF measurement systems (script used for automation using python). I also led the analysis, design and implementation of software tools and systems used for data collection.

EDUCATION

University Of Washington
June 21 – December 21

Certificate in Full stack Web Development

University Of Washington October 2016 – June 2018 *Master in Business Administration*

University Of Washington October 1993 – June 1995 *Master in Electrical Engineering*

EXPERIENCE

Independent Web Developer

2017 - Current

- Integrate code changes, test code changes, and document code changes
- Developed PHP scripts to translate data between applications
- Developed automation scripts to test storage appliances in Python
- Practice agile development methodologies and work with current networking technologies
- Built website and make modification with php and Mysql
- Wrote php scripts to load data and parse Api responses

The Boeing Company

2005 - Current

- Wrote, modified, and debugged internal website for custom application
- Wrote scripts to interface with measurement equipments
- Developed HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and JSP pages for user interaction
- Wrote Python scripts to load data and parse XML documents

SKILLS

- Full stack Web developer certificate
- Javascript
- Linux
- Php
- MySql
- Html
- Jquery
- Css